Guide to the Greenwich House Records TAM.139
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Administrative Records
  - Subseries E: Personnel Records
    - Sub-subseries 2: Residents
      - Flemming, Mae, 1922-1923 (Box 12, Folder 58)
      - Fletcher, Joseph, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 59)
      - Flethcher, Virginia, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 60)
      - Foley, Jule, 1924 (Box 12, Folder 61)
      - Ford, Judson, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 62)
      - Forster, R. Halford, 1930-1931 (Box 12, Folder 63)
      - Foster, Nellie, 1925-1926 (Box 12, Folder 64)
      - Fraser, Alice, 1929 (Box 12, Folder 65)
      - Fraser, Mary, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 66)
      - Frederiksen, Felix, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 67)
      - Fredericksen, Laura, 1923-1927 (Box 12, Folder 68)
      - Frisbee, Lloyd, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 69)
      - Fritchey, Ethel, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 70)
      - Frost, Lillian, 1929-1930 (Box 12, Folder 71)
      - Fry, Eva, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Fuller, Lady, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Galt, Alice, 1922-1923 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Gardner, Sarah, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Garrett, Elizabeth, 1933-1935 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Garrettson, Jane, 1932-1933 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Gaunt, Ernest, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Geissler, Louise, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - George, Norma and Kathleen Morrison, 1931 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Gilbert, Margaret, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Gilbert, Ruth, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Gilbreth, Ernestine, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Gillian, Susan, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Gilman, Jean, 1931 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Gilmore, William, 1935-1936 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Glover, Milton, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Gordon, Melvin, 1940-1941 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Gordon, O'Neal, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Gorman, Agnes, 1925-1926 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Gossen, Erika, 1925-1927 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Grane, Jean, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Graves, Phyllis, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - Gray, Eleanor, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - Gray, Lucy, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - Gray, Marian, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - Graydon, Gertrude, 1919 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - Greely, Antoinette, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 27)
      - Green, Herbert, 1932-1933 (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - Green, Verona, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 29)
      - Greene, Richard, 1928-1929 (Box 13, Folder 30)
      - Griffin, Jane, 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 31)
      - Griffith, Marion, 1931 (Box 13, Folder 32)
      - Grimmell, Carolyn, 1922-1923 (Box 13, Folder 33)
      - Grinnell, Albert, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 34)
      - Grover, Olive, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 35)
      - Grubnau, Louise, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 36)
      - Gruener, Adele, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 37)
      - Grumpelt, Helen, 1932-1933 (Box 13, Folder 38)
      - Grunewald, Richard, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 39)
      - Gunn, Mildred, 1926-1928 (Box 13, Folder 40)
      - Gurin, Dorothy, 1935-1936 (Box 13, Folder 41)
      - Haines, Marian, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 42)
      - Hall, Geraldine, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 43)
      - Hall, Ruth, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 44)
      - Hall, W.V., 1932 (Box 13, Folder 45)
      - Hamilton, Katherine, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 46)
      - Hamlin, Julia, 1938-1940 (Box 13, Folder 47)
      - Hankinson, Edith, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 48)
      - Hanna, Muriel, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 49)
      - Harper, William, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 50)
      - Harris, Anne, 1933-1934 (Box 13, Folder 51)
      - Harris, Joyce, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 52)
      - Harris, Muriel, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 53)
      - Hart, Ethel, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 54)
      - Havlon, Mary Long, 1931 (Box 13, Folder 55)
      - Hawthorne, Verna, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 56)
      - Hay, Jean, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 57)
      - Hecht, Ilse, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 58)
      - Heckaman, Rosamond, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 59)
      - Hennaman, Lillian, 1921 (Box 13, Folder 60)
      - Henrickson, Merle, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 61)
      - Henry, Dorothy, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 62)
      - Henry, Lucille, 1930-1931 (Box 13, Folder 63)
      - Herron, Horace, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 64)
      - Hibberd, Elizabeth, 1921 (Box 13, Folder 65)
      - Hill, Louise, 1926 (Box 13, Folder 66)
      - Hill, Louise, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 67)
      - Hilles, W.T., 1923 (Box 13, Folder 68)
      - Hilliker, William P., 1926-1927 (Box 13, Folder 69)
      - Hope, Marjorie, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 70)
      - Howard, James, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 71)
      - Howe, Paul French, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 72)
      - Hogan, Raymond, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 73)
      - Homer, Anne, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 74)
      - Hovde, Helen, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Hoyt, Elizabeth, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Hubbard, Kathryn, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Hughett, Lucille, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Hull, Raymona, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Hunter, Beatrice, 1922-1925 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Hurley, Julia, 1923-1925 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Hutchinson, Mary, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Hutton, Sara, 1931-1932 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Jackson, Isabel, 1922-1923 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Jacoby, Kathleen, 1928 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - James, Mary, 1931-1934 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - James, Vera, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Jeffers, Walter, 1936-1939 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Jenks, Elizabeth, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Jillard, Ruth, 1932-1933 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - Johnesse, Adaline, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - Johnston, Geraldine, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - Jones, Anne Cutting, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - Jones, Margaret, 1935-1940 (Box 14, Folder 20)
        Reel 14 (MN# 2195)
      - Jones, Minna Lee, 1928-1929 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Jones, Virginia Lee, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - Joslyn, Magda, 1931-1932 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - Joyce, Alice, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 24)
      - Judkins, Barbara, 1930-1931 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - Kahn, Julietta, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - Keen, Harold, 1927-1928 (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - Kimball, Lewis, 1925-1926 (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - Kinsolving, Mary, 1926 (Box 14, Folder 29)
      - Klintberg, Gertrud, 1926 (Box 14, Folder 30)
      - Knowlton, Elizabeth, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 31)
      - Koempel, Leslie, 1931 (Box 14, Folder 32)
      - Kolokoski, Louis, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 33)
      - Krohn, Lawrence, 1925 (Box 14, Folder 34)
      - Kuder, Merle, 1930-1931 (Box 14, Folder 35)
      - Kullman, Elma, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 36)
      - Lambert, Robert and Sylvia, 1921-1922 (Box 14, Folder 37)
      - Lambrecht, Beatrice, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 38)
      - Langstroth, Ivan, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 39)
      - Lanier, Ruby, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 40)
      - Latimer, Elizabeth, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 41)
      - Lawton, Frances, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 42)
      - Lee, Mary, 1920-1922 (Box 14, Folder 43)
      - Leizear, Elizabeth, 1932-1934 (Box 14, Folder 44)
      - Letton, Francis, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 45)
      - Lewin-Guradze, Heinz, 1937-1938 (Box 14, Folder 46)
      - Lewis, Read, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 47)
      - Liebert, Peter, 1939-1940 (Box 14, Folder 48)
      - Light, Gertrude, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 49)
      - London, Leah, 1927 (Box 14, Folder 50)
      - Long, Doris, 1923-1926 (Box 14, Folder 51)
      - Love, Katherine, 1937-1938 (Box 14, Folder 52)
      - Luklova, Eva, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 53)
      - Lund, Harald, 1922-1926 (Box 14, Folder 54)
      - Lyman, Mary, 1934-1935 (Box 14, Folder 55)
      - Lyon, Evelyn Mary, 1931 (Box 14, Folder 56)
      - Lytton, Henry D., 1939 (Box 14, Folder 57A)
      - Clarissa, Macavoy, 1931-1932 (Box 14, Folder 57B)
      - MacDonald, Clara, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 58)
      - Mack, Lois, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 59)
      - Mackemer, Dorothy and Joseph, 1923-1927 (Box 14, Folder 60)
      - Magill, Ellen, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 61)
      - Mahn, Kathryn, 1925-1926 (Box 14, Folder 62)
      - Manning, William, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 63)
      - Many, Katharine, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 64)
      - Marbourg, Helen- Mills College Students, 1931 (Box 14, Folder 65)
      - Margolis, Laura, 1927 (Box 14, Folder 66)
      - Markham, Mary Catherine, 1918-1924 (Box 14, Folder 67)
      - Marsh, Benjamin, 1925 (Box 14, Folder 68)
      - Marsh, Janet, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 69)
      - Marshall, Madaline, 1927 (Box 14, Folder 70)
      - Martin, Inez, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 71)
      - Martin, Janet, 1924-1932 (Box 14, Folder 72)
      - Martin, Mary, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 73)
      - Masterson, Harriet, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Matheson, Cecile, 1924-1925 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Matthew, H. C., 1928 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - May, Roswell, 1925-1928 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Maynard, Carolyn, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - McCarthy, Ethel, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - McCleary, Fiona, 1928 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - McClintock, Betty, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - McCormick, Elsie, 1923-1924 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - McCoy, Bruce, 1930-1934 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - McDonald, Lillian, 1928-1929 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - McFetridge, Edward, ca.1938 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - McGarry, Anna and Lillian Marburg, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - McGerr, Gerald C., 1931-1933 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - McGuire, Winona, 1930-1931 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - McKay, Mildred, 1921 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - McKeon, Anne, 1934 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - McKnight, Katharine, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - McLean, Mary Pierson, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - McManus, Joseph, 1933-1935 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - McNall, Lucy, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - Mead, Philip, 1930-1931 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      - Melton, Kinsey, 1927-1929 (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - Michaelis, Wilhelm, 1939-1940 (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - Miller, Berti, 1927 (Box 15, Folder 25)
      - Miller, Mary M, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - Minger, Harold, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 27)
      - Moffat, Susann, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 28)
      - Mohr, Irma, 1929-1931 (Box 15, Folder 29)
      - Moore, Beatrix, 1927 (Box 15, Folder 30)
      - Moore, Thomas, 1924-1925 (Box 15, Folder 31)
      - More, Louise, 1924-1933 (Box 15, Folder 32)
      - Morris, T. Raymond, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 33)
      - Morrison, Charlotte, 1922-1926 (Box 15, Folder 34)
      - Morten, Georgia, 1923-1924 (Box 15, Folder 35)
      - Moses, Beatrice, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 36)
      - Moss, Margaret, 1919-1920 (Box 15, Folder 37)
      - Moulton, Corinne, 1923 (Box 15, Folder 38)
      - Muirhead, John, 1921 (Box 15, Folder 39)
      - Murray, Evelyn, 1928 (Box 15, Folder 40)
      - Norden, Carl, 1929 (Box 15, Folder 41)
      - Norris, Rosemary, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 42)
      - Northcutt, Shelby, 1927 (Box 15, Folder 43)
      - Nyhart, Natalie, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 44)
      - O'Brien, Agnes, 1923-1925 (Box 15, Folder 45)
      - O'Brien, Mary, 1927 (Box 15, Folder 46)
      - O'Connor, Zena, 1922-1923 (Box 15, Folder 47)
      - O'Dwyer, Elizabeth, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 48)
      - O'Hara, Loftus, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 49)
      - Oliver, Mildred, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 50)
      - Orr, William E., 1930-1934 (Box 15, Folder 51)
      - Ostry, Ethel, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 52)
      - Oxley, Wallace, 1931-1932 (Box 15, Folder 53)
      - Palmer, Anne, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 54)
        Reel 15 (MN# 2196)
      - Papivean, Marguerite, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 55)
      - Parke, Harry, 1922 (Box 15, Folder 56)
      - Parker, Edith, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 57)
      - Parker, E. L., 1937 (Box 15, Folder 58)
      - Patton, Francis, 1919-1920 (Box 15, Folder 59)
      - Payne, John, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 60)
      - Pearson, Mary, 1922-1923 (Box 15, Folder 61)
      - Perry, Evelyn, 1929 (Box 15, Folder 62)
      - Petrella, Tommaso, 1932-1933 (Box 15, Folder 63)
      - Phillips, Jackson, 1922-1923 (Box 15, Folder 64)
      - Pierce, Ross, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 65)
      - Pike, Lucile, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 66)
      - Pilkington, A. W., 1937-1938 (Box 15, Folder 67)
      - Plum, Margaret, 1924-1927 (Box 15, Folder 68)
      - Polk, Julia, 1934 (Box 15, Folder 69)
      - Pollak, Wilma, 1907 (Box 15, Folder 70)
      - Porter, Grace, 1929 (Box 15, Folder 71)
      - Porter, Mary, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Power, Elise, 1930-1932 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Prevo, Nancy, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Priestly, Alice, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Puce, Elizabeth, 1917-1920 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Purnell, Maude, 1924-1925 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Putnam, Persis, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Ratcliffe, Francis, 1924 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Ratner, Sallie, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Read, Goodrich, 1922-1923 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Reynolds, Welden, 1929-1930 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Ridge, Margaret, 1928-1930 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Ripley, Bettina, 1929-1933 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Ritchey, Adessa, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Ritchie, G. Wells, 1930-1931 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Robbins, Alice, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Robinson, Frances, 1928 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Rosebrugh, Eleanor, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Rosensteil, Isabelle, 1925-1927 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Ross, George, 1932-1933 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Ross, Henrietta Lund, 1927-1931 (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - Rossman, Elizabeth, 1933-1934 (Box 16, Folder 22)
      - Rubinow, Laura, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 23)
      - Rubinstein, Dosha, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 24)
      - Ruggles, Anne, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 25)
      - Rushmore, Dorothea, 1924 (Box 16, Folder 26)
      - Russell, E.B., 1925 (Box 16, Folder 27)
      - Ryan, Clare, 1928 (Box 16, Folder 28)
      - Smith, Mary, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 29)
      - Steinberg, Esther, 1920 (Box 16, Folder 30)
      - Stetter, Henry G., 1930-1931 (Box 16, Folder 31)
      - Stephens, Donald, 1928 (Box 16, Folder 32)
      - Stewart, Rosa, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 33)
      - Stripe, Jack, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 34)
      - Stofer, Cornelia, 1927-1928 (Box 16, Folder 35)
      - Stoflet, Ada, 1931-1932 (Box 16, Folder 36)
      - Stolberg, Benjamin, 1923-1925 (Box 16, Folder 37)
      - Stratton, Elenore, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 38)
      - Sullivan, Jamesss, 1935-1936 (Box 16, Folder 39)
      - Surtes, Flora, 1925-1926 (Box 16, Folder 40)
      - Swan, Catherine, 1924-1928 (Box 16, Folder 41)
      - Swift, Ruth, 1930-1931 (Box 16, Folder 42)
      - Sycle, Magaret, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 43)
      - Symmes, Marion, 1923-1924 (Box 16, Folder 44)
      - Talbot, Lillis, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 45)
      - Talbot, Mira, 1924-1926 (Box 16, Folder 46)
      - Tapia, Simona, 1924-1925 (Box 16, Folder 47)
      - Taylor, Eleanore, 1927 (Box 16, Folder 48)
      - Taylor, Jeanne, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 49)
      - Taylor, Mary, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 50)
      - Thomas, Elizabeth, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 51)
      - Thompson, Ruth, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 52)
      - Tilley, Laurence, 1927 (Box 16, Folder 53)
      - Titcomb, Margaret, 1924-1927 (Box 16, Folder 54)
      - Travers, Robert, 1940-1941 (Box 16, Folder 55)
      - Trout, Bessie, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 56)
      - Tree, Gladys, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 57)
      - Trump, Ross, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 58)
      - Tupper, Mary, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 59)
      - Turpin, Evelyn, 1926-1927 (Box 16, Folder 60)
      - Tyler, Sally, 1935-1936 (Box 16, Folder 61)
      - Vanderveer, Helen, 1927 (Box 16, Folder 62)
      - Van Eeghen, L., 1925 (Box 16, Folder 63)
      - Van Fleet, Josephine, 1928 (Box 16, Folder 64)
      - Vanuxen, Marguerite, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 65)
      - Vondrack, Olga, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 66)
      - Walker, John P., 1924-1928 (Box 16, Folder 67)
      - Wallace, Mary, 1929-1941 (Box 16, Folder 68)
      - Wallace, Thomas, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 69)
      - Wardell, Margaret, 1922-1925 (Box 16, Folder 70)
      - Warner, Percy, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 71)
      - Wasson, Iva, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 72)
      - Watson, Thelma, 1933-1934 (Box 16, Folder 73)
      - Weakes, Mabel, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 74)
      - Weaver, Persis, 1929-1930 (Box 16, Folder 75)
      - Weinlick, Elsie, 1943 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Weiss, Victor, 1926-1927 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Wesley, John, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - White, Virginia, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Whitelaw, Jean, 1926-1927 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Whitley, Joyce, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Whyte, Lucy, 1923-1926 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Wiesman, Margaret, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Wilder, Charlotte, 1931-1932 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Wiley, June, 1935-1936 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Wilkinson, Gladys, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Williams, Constance, 1930 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Williams, Elsie, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Williams, Rosalie, 1931 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Williamson, Ada, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Willison, Nel, 1922-1924 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Wills, David, 1929 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Wilson, David, 1935 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Wilson, Joseph, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Wilson, Mira, 1929 (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Wise, Randolph, 1938-1940 (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - Witter, Elizabeth, 1919-1921 (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - Woodhouse, Elizabeth, 1928 (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - Woodall, Doris, 1922-1923 (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - Woodward, Florence, 1926-1927 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - Woolley, Isabelle, 1917-1921 (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - Wooster-Hull, Katherine, 1930-1931 (Box 17, Folder 27)
      - Wootton, Barbara, 1930 (Box 17, Folder 28)
      - Worden, Allison, 1936-1937 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - Wormser, Irma, 1929 (Box 17, Folder 30)
      - Wright, Ann, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 31)
      - Wright, Charles, 1934-1936 (Box 17, Folder 32)
      - Yeatman, Mary Jane, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 33)
      - Young, Florence, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 34)
      - Yoshimi, Shizu, 1928 (Box 17, Folder 35)
      - Zurfluh, Ruth and John, 1929 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Sub-subseries 3: Volunteers
      - Applications for Volunteer Work (accepted), 1922-1924 (Box 17, Folder 37)
        Reel 16 (MN# 2197)
      - Applications for Volunteer Work- Camp Herbert Parsons, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 38)
      - Assistant Director Helen F. Johnson- Volunteer Lists, 1933-1934 (Box 17, Folder 39)
      - Assistant Director Helen F. Johnson- Volunteer Correspondence, 1933-1934 (Box 17, Folder 40)
      - Applications for Volunteer Work, Oct 1933-Sep 1934 (Box 17, Folder 41)
      - Applications for Volunteer Work- Camp Herbert Parsons, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 42)
      - Applications for Volunteer Work, Oct 1934-Sep 1935 (Box 17, Folder 43)
      - Applications for Volunteer Work, Oct 1935-Sep 1936 (Box 17, Folder 44)
      - Applications for Volunteer Work (accepted), Oct 1936-Sep 1937 (Box 17, Folder 45)
      - Applications for Volunteer Work, Oct 1937-Sep 1938 (Box 17, Folder 46)
      - Applications for Volunteer Work (with rosters), Oct 1938-Sep 1939 (Box 17, Folder 47)
      - Applications for Volunteer Work, Oct 1939-Sep 1940 (Box 17, Folder 48)
      - Applications for Volunteer Work, Oct 1940-Sep 1941 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Subseries F: Addendum
    - Board of Managers-List, 1944 (Box 17A, Folder 1)
      Items not microfilmed
    - Financial Records-Budget, 1928-1932 (Box 17A, Folder 2)
    - Workshops-Budgets and Salaries, 1929-1932 (Box 17A, Folder 3)
    - Treasurer' Correspondence, 1909-1912 (Box 17A, Folder 4)
    - Treasurer's Correspondence-Kauth Appeals, 1939-1940, 1947 (Box 17A, Folder 5)
    - Treasurer's Correspondence-Kauth Appeals, Reports, 1940 (Box 17A, Folder 6)
    - Clara Clapp, Director of Finance; Correspondence-Dorr, John V.N., 1939-1942 (Box 17A, Folder 7)
    - Clara Clapp, Director of Finance; Fund-Raising Plan, 1934 (Box 17A, Folder 8)
    - Clara Clapp, Director of Finance; Metcalf, Manton B., 1925-1943 (Box 17A, Folder 9)
    - Clara Clapp, Director of Finance; Music School Mortgage, 1935-1936, 1940 (Box 17A, Folder 10)
    - Clara Clapp, Director of Finance; Correspondence-Scheftel, Herbert, 1940-1941 (Box 17A, Folder 11)
    - Ruth Ricks and Helen Feldman-Financial Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 17A, Folder 12)
    - Financial Report, 1941 (Box 17A, Folder 13)
    - Financial Records-Salaries, 1929-1932 (Box 17A, Folder 14)
    - Financial Statements, 1935-1936 (Box 17A, Folder 15)
    - Financial Records, Ledger-Income and Expenses, 1924 (Box 17A, Folder 16)
    - Rent Register, 1943-1944 (Box 17A, Folder 17)
    - Contribution Correspondence-Foundations: Avalon Foundation, 1943-1953 (Box 17A, Folder 18)
    - Contribution Correspondence-Foundations: Baird Foundation, 1951-1955 (Box 17A, Folder 19)
    - Contribution Correspondence-Foundations: Charles E. Culpepper Foundation, 1946-1953 (Box 17A, Folder 20)
    - Contribution Correspondence-Foundations: John Dorr and Antoinette Dorr-Hardon Trust, 1943-1955 (Box 17A, Folder 21)
    - Contribution Correspondence-Foundations: Hayden Foundation, 1937-1948 (Box 17A, Folder 22)
    - Contribution Correspondence-Foundations: Turrell Fund, 1947-1956 (Box 17A, Folder 23)
    - Fund Raising Letters and Reports, 1931 (Box 17A, Folder 24)
    - Fund Raising Letters, 1937-1939 (Box 17A, Folder 25)
    - Fund Raising Letters, undated, 1938-1944 (Box 17A, Folder 26)
    - Fund Raising Letters, 1940-1944 (Box 17A, Folder 27)
    - Fund Raising Letters, 1941-1946 (Box 17A, Folder 28)
    - Contribution Correspondence: Greater New York Fund, 1944-1953 (Box 17A, Folder 29)
    - Contribution Correspondence: Greater New York Fund-GH Annual Reports to Fund, 1945-1948 (Box 17A, Folder 30)
    - Contribution Correspondence: Havens Relief Fund, 1942-1953 (Box 17A, Folder 31)
    - Contribution Correspondence: New York Community Trust, 1938-1953 (Box 17A, Folder 32)
    - Contribution Correspondence: New York University, 1946-1954 (Box 17A, Folder 33)
    - Personnel: Directories-Lists of Staff, 1929-1942 (Box 17A, Folder 34)
    - Personnel Policies, ca.1930, 1946 (Box 17A, Folder 35)
    - Personnel Policies, 1953 (Box 17A, Folder 36)
    - Paid Workers: A, 1919-1932 (Box 17A, Folder 37)
    - Paid Workers: A, 1935-1951 (Box 17A, Folder 38)
    - Paid Workers: Backes-Blair, 1923-1939 (Box 17A, Folder 39)
    - Paid Workers: Blatt-Butts, 1926-1931 (Box 17A, Folder 40)
    - Paid Workers: B, 1926-1951 (Box 17A, Folder 41)
    - Paid Workers: G, 1951 (Box 17A, Folder 42)
    - Paid Workers: H, 1942-1950 (Box 17A, Folder 43)
    - Paid Workers: I-K, 1928-1953 (Box 17A, Folder 44)
    - Paid Workers: L, 1940-1952 (Box 17A, Folder 45)
    - Paid Workers: Lohman, John Frederick, 1939-1943 (Box 17A, Folder 46)
    - Paid Workers: MacGowan, Eleanor, 1923-1950 (Box 17A, Folder 47)
    - Paid Workers: Murphy, Helen, 1922-1951 (Box 17A, Folder 48)
    - Paid Workers: M-O, 1926-1949 (Box 17A, Folder 49)
    - Paid Workers: P, 1927-1949 (Box 17A, Folder 50)
    - Paid Workers: Q-S, 1924-1953 (Box 17A, Folder 51)
    - Paid Workers: Torrup, Ingeborg, 1932-1952 (Box 17A, Folder 52)
    - Paid Workers:T-Z, 1931-1952 (Box 17A, Folder 53)
    - Residents: Residents' House Committee-Financial Statements, 1939-1943 (Box 17A, Folder 54)
    - Residents: List of Residents, 1952 (Box 17A, Folder 55)
    - Residents: Residents' Meetings-Minutes, Reules for Residents, 1938-1952, undated (Box 17A, Folder 56)
    - Residents: Residents' Manual, ca.1946 (Box 17A, Folder 57)
    - Residents: Residents' Manual, ca.1948 (Box 17A, Folder 58)
    - Residents: Directors' Memos and Correspondence with Residents; Cost of Residents' Program, 1946-1953 (Box 17A, Folder 59)
    - Residents: A-B, 1931-1954 (Box 17A, Folder 60)
    - Residents: C, 1927-1951 (Box 17A, Folder 61)
    - Residents: D-E, 1948-1952 (Box 17A, Folder 62)
    - Residents: F, 1945-1954 (Box 17B, Folder 1)
    - Residents: G, 1944-1950 (Box 17B, Folder 2)
    - Residents: H, 1943-1954 (Box 17B, Folder 3)